http://www.ajhs.org/privacy-policy

Skip to main content
American Jewish Historical Society
Search this site
Ask a reference questionSearch collections...
Privacy Policy
Privacy PolicyIntroductionWe have created this statement to demonstrate our firm commitment to your privacy. We do not collect personally identifying information about you when you visit our site, unless you choose to provide such information to us. Providing such information is strictly voluntary. This policy is your guide to how we will handle information we learn about you from your visit to our Web site.Use of LinksThroughout our Web pages, we provide links to other servers which may contain information of interest to our readers. We take no responsibility for, and exercise no control over, the organizations, views, or accuracy of the information contained on other servers. Creating a text link from your Web site to our site does not require permission, provided that your link to this site is presented in a manner that does not give the impression that the American Jewish Historical Society is making either an express or implied endorsement of the content or service provided on your Web site. If you have a link you'd like us to consider adding to our Web site, please send an email to reference@ajhs.org with the subject "Link request." Use of Text and ImagesIf you would like to publish information that you find on our Web site, please send your request to reference@ajhs.org. AccessibilityThis Web site is designed to be accessible to visitors with disabilities, and to comply with federal guidelines concerning accessibility. We welcome your comments. If you have suggestions on how to make the site more accessible, please contact us at reference@ajhs.org. Reading or DownloadingWe collect and store only the following information about you: the name of the domain from which you access the Internet (for example, aol.com, if you are connecting from an America Online account), the date and time you access our site, and the Internet address of the Web site from which you linked to our site.We use the information we collect to measure the number of visitors to the different sections of our site, and to help us make our site more useful to visitors. Sending us an EmailYou also may decide to send us personally identifying information, for example, in an electronic mail message containing a question or comment, or by filling out a Web form that provides us this information. We use personally identifying information from email primarily to respond to your requests. We may forward your email to other employees who are better able to answer your questions. We may also use your email to contact you in the future about our programs that may be of interest.We want to be very clear: We will not obtain personally identifying information about you when you visit our site, unless you choose to provide such information to us. Providing such information is strictly voluntary. Except as might be required by law, we do not share any information we receive with any outside parties.If you sign up for one of our email lists, we will only send you the kinds of information you have requested. We won't share your email address with any outside parties. Change Your Contact InformationYou may choose to receive only specific communications or none at all. To unsubscribe from mail or email, you may send an email to development@ajhs.org. You cannot remove yourself from our database, but you can prevent unwanted communication. If you have any questions about this privacy statement, you can contact us info@ajhs.org.
Ask an ArchivistView our ProgramsMake a DonationJoin our Mailing List
Search collections...
©2019 American Jewish Historical Society. All Rights Reserved. Terms and Policies | Sitemap
